marketpressrelease.com 2019-06-22

# Press Release Submission And Distribution Service - MarketPressRelease.com

MarketPressRelease takes data privacy seriously. This privacy policy explains who we are, how we collect, share and use Personal Information, and how you can exercise your privacy rights. 

We recommend that you read this privacy policy in full to ensure you are fully informed. If you have any questions or concerns about our use of your Personal Information, then please contact us at support@marketpressrelease.com

**Key Terms**  
In this privacy policy, these terms have the following meanings:

**"Distribution List"** is a list of Contacts and their email ids of those who have subscribed to our newsletter or our RSS Feeds directly and / or through Google Feeders.

**"Member"** means any person or entity that is registered with us to use the Services.

**"Personal Information"** means any information that identifies or can be used to identify a Member, a Contact, or a Visitor, directly or indirectly. Examples of Personal Information include, but are not limited to, first and last name, email address, designation, address, contact no. or other demographic information.

**"Website(s)"** means any website(s) we own and operate (such as www.marketpressrelease.com) or any web pages.

**"Visitor"** means any person who visits any of our Websites.

**"you"** and **"your"** means, depending on the context, either a Member, a Contact, or a Visitor.

**Information We Collect**  
The Personal Information that we may collect broadly falls into the following categories:

**Registration information:** You need a MarketPressRelease account to use the Services as a Member. When you register for an account, you will be asked to provide certain basic information, such as your name, email address, username, password, company name, designation, address, and phone number. 

**Billing and communications information:** If you purchase our Services, you may also need to provide us with payment and billing information, such as your company registration details and billing address.

**Device information:** We collect information about the device and applications you use to access the Services, such as your IP address. Various similar information will be gather by Google Analytics which includes your operating system, your browser ID, your phone device and other information about your system and connection.

**Use of Information**  
We may use the Personal Information we collect through the Services or other sources for a range of reasons, including:

**To bill and collect money:** This includes sending you emails, invoices, receipts, notices of delinquency, and alerting you.

**To send you system alert Emails:** This includes sending you emails to inform you about your account, about your submitted press release, service changes, releases, abuse reports etc.

**To provide service and support:** We will use your company and personal details in order to full-fill our services and provide support when you need it.

_Updated on May 23rd 2018_
